Guide to the Fred Friendly Papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series VIII: Media, 1961-1991
  - Videotapes
    - Liveline --"Fred Friendly", 1985, (Umatic tape) (Box 215)
    - Murrow: The Movie, undated, (Umatic tape); (2 tapes) (Box 215)
    - PBS Problem-Based Learning, 1968-1990, (VHS tape); (4 tapes) (Box 215)
    - Murrow Farewell to CBS, 1961 January 31 (Box 215)
    - MSS: Reading, Writing, and Religion by KUED Channel 7 Salt Lake City, 1984 May 10, (Umatic tape) (Box 215)
    - "Tonkin Gulf", undated, (VHS tape) (Box 215)
    - TV Academy Hall of Fame --"Murrow", 1989, (VHS tape) (Box 215)